Sabrina, Down Under is a tv movie, comedy, fantasy
film directed by Kenneth R. Koch.
Sabrina travels to Australia's Great Barrier Reef with her best friend Gwen, a fellow witch from England, for a week-long vacation where they try to help protect a
hidden mermaid colony whose habitat is threatened by ocean pollution, and by a local marine biologist determined to find the colony as his claim to fame.
While Sabrina finds romance with a "merman" from the mermaid colony, Salem the cat finds a possible romance with
another witch-turned-into-a-cat, named Hilary, but finds Sabrina's problems interfering with his plans.
Sabrina Spellman, played by Melissa Joan Hart.
Gwen, played by Tara Strong.
Barnaby, played by Scott Michaelson.
Fin, played by Lindsay Sloane.
Salem Saberhagen (voice), played by Nick Bakay.
Dr. Julian Martin, played by Peter O'Brien.
Sabrina Down Under is a 1999 American television film
produced for ABC, airing on September 26, 1999.
It is a sequel to Sabrina Goes to Rome and is a companion to
the Sabrina the Teenage Witch television series.
The film features only two characters from the television series: teenage witch Sabrina Spellman
(played by Melissa Joan Hart), and talking cat Salem Saberhagen (voiced by Nick Bakay).
Lindsay Sloane was also a regular actress in the television
series, but plays a different character in this film.
Tara Charendoff reprises her role as Gwen from Sabrina Goes to Rome.
As the film is set in Australia, none of the scenes are filmed
on the original set of the television series.
The film was directed by Kenneth R.
Koch, who helped to produce Sabrina Goes to Rome.
He also directed many episodes of the television series
and was a prominent producer of the show.
Unlike Sabrina Goes to Rome, which is included in the season 7 DVD release of the Sabrina the Teenage
Witch television series, Sabrina Down Under was not included in any of the season sets.
It was later released on a stand-alone DVD on February 7, 2017.
Prior to this, the film  was released on VHS.
It is available to stream on Hulu.
The film explores themes of witch, australia, ocean, marine biologist, mermaid.
The tone is lighthearted.